<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wellness and mental health on Student Wellbeing</title>
    <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wellness and mental health on Student Wellbeing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Strategy</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/strategy/</guid>
      <description>Our mental health strategy UM&amp;rsquo;s Campus Mental Health Strategy, Success Through Wellness, is a call to action for all of us as students, staff and faculty within the UM community.
The strategy focuses on the promotion and support of mental health as a collective responsibility. It examines all aspects of the university, and identifies ways we can be a community that is committed, caring, healthy, responsive, supportive and resourceful.
Supporting mental health and well-being reaps tremendous rewards, including a more positive work and learning environment, enhanced student experience, and increased staff and faculty satisfaction and engagement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faculty and staff well-beings</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/get_support/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/get_support/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Wellness encompasses mental, spiritual, physical, financial, family and workplace health. Discover programs and resources available to support your wellness journey and improve well-being. (Access on UM Intranet with your @umanitoba.ca employee email address.)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/faq/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.
1. WHAT TO DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student health and wellness</title>
      <link>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/get_support/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lttt.github.io/studentWellbeingv2/get_support/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Health and wellness play a critical role in student success. Explore a wide range of services that are available to you that support your physical and mental well-being.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
